{
  "users": [
    {
      "id": "4ee8",
      "firstName": "sss",
      "mailType": "Office",
      "mail": "sss@gmail.com",
      "phnNo": "1234567890",
      "dob": "2025-04-09",
      "addr": "qwerty",
      "pwd": "123456"
    },
    {
      "id": "189a",
      "firstName": "supree",
      "mailType": "Office",
      "mail": "supree@gmail.com",
      "phnNo": "1234567890",
      "dob": "2025-04-09",
      "addr": "qwertyu",
      "pwd": "123456"
    },
    {
      "id": "e4c9",
      "firstName": "sup",
      "mailType": "Office",
      "mail": "supb@deloitte.com",
      "phnNo": "1234567890",
      "dob": "2025-04-09",
      "addr": "qwerty",
      "pwd": "123456"
    },
    {
      "id": "9e2d",
      "firstName": "supreetha",
      "mailType": "Office",
      "mail": "supreetha@gmail.com",
      "phnNo": "1234567890",
      "dob": "2005-10-25",
      "addr": "qwert",
      "pwd": "123456"
    }
  ],
  "quizzes": [
    {
      "id": "3591",
      "title": "angular",
      "startDate": "2025-04-09",
      "endDate": "13",
      "questions": [
        {
          "question": " Which version of Angular marked the shift from AngularJS to Angular?",
          "options": [
            "2",
            "3",
            "4",
            "6"
          ],
          "correctAnswer": "2"
        }
      ],
      "answers": [
        "2"
      ],
      "attendedTime": "25/4/2025, 11:16:19 am",
      "submitted": true,
      "selectedAnswers": {
        "0": "2"
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "b684",
      "title": "angular",
      "startDate": "2025-04-25",
      "endDate": "1",
      "questions": [
        {
          "question": " Angular is primarily maintained by which company?",
          "options": [
            "am",
            "fb",
            "g",
            "fl"
          ],
          "correctAnswer": "g"
        }
      ],
      "answers": [
        "g"
      ],
      "attendedTime": "25/4/2025, 10:27:18 am",
      "submitted": true
    },
    {
      "id": "513e",
      "title": "ang",
      "startDate": "2025-04-25",
      "endDate": "2025-04-26",
      "questions": [
        {
          "question": " Which file extension is used for Angular component templates?",
          "options": [
            "html",
            "ts",
            "js",
            "css"
          ],
          "correctAnswer": "js"
        }
      ],
      "answers": [
        "ts"
      ],
      "attendedTime": "25/4/2025, 10:17:20 am",
      "submitted": true
    },
    {
      "id": "4a8b",
      "title": "ang",
      "startDate": "2025-04-26",
      "endDate": "2025-04-26",
      "questions": [
        {
          "question": " Which Angular feature is used to display data in a component template dynamically?",
          "options": [
            "service",
            "pipe",
            "module",
            "directive"
          ],
          "correctAnswer": "directive"
        }
      ],
      "answers": [
        "module"
      ],
      "attendedTime": "25/4/2025, 9:59:51 am",
      "submitted": true
    },
    {
      "id": "2740",
      "title": "Node",
      "startDate": "2025-04-25",
      "endDate": "2025-04-25",
      "questions": [
        {
          "question": " Which Angular feature is used to display data in a component template dynamically?",
          "options": [
            "1",
            "2",
            "3",
            "4"
          ],
          "correctAnswer": ""
        }
      ],
      "answers": [
        "2"
      ],
      "attendedTime": "25/4/2025, 10:27:09 am",
      "submitted": true
    },
    {
      "id": "c749",
      "title": "Angular_Exam",
      "startDate": "2025-04-25",
      "endDate": "2025-04-25",
      "questions": [
        {
          "question": "Which version of Angular marked the shift from AngularJS to Angular?",
          "options": [
            "2",
            "4",
            "6",
            "8"
          ],
          "correctAnswer": "2"
        }
      ],
      "answers": [
        "2"
      ],
      "attendedTime": "25/4/2025, 9:55:30 am",
      "submitted": true
    },
    {
      "id": "52fd",
      "title": "Final_Exam",
      "startDate": "2025-04-26",
      "endDate": "2025-04-26",
      "questions": [
        {
          "question": "Which version of Angular marked the shift from AngularJS to Angular?",
          "options": [
            "v2",
            "v3",
            "v5",
            "v4"
          ],
          "correctAnswer": "v2"
        },
        {
          "question": "Angular is primarily maintained by which company?",
          "options": [
            "flipkart",
            "microsoft",
            "Amazon",
            "Google"
          ],
          "correctAnswer": "Google"
        }
      ],
      "answers": [
        "v2",
        "Google"
      ],
      "attendedTime": "25/4/2025, 10:44:06 am",
      "submitted": true
    },
    {
      "id": "4518",
      "title": "Quiz_Angular",
      "startDate": "2025-04-25",
      "endDate": "2025-04-25",
      "questions": [
        {
          "question": " Which command is used to serve an Angular application locally for development?",
          "options": [
            "serve",
            "start",
            "run",
            "init"
          ],
          "correctAnswer": "serve"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": "38ed",
      "userId": "e4c9",
      "title": "Java",
      "startDate": "2025-04-26",
      "endDate": "2025-04-26",
      "questions": [
        {
          "question": "what is java extension",
          "options": [
            "html",
            "ts",
            "js",
            "java"
          ],
          "correctAnswer": "java"
        }
      ],
      "submitted": false
    },
    {
      "id": "ba75",
      "userId": "e4c9",
      "title": "example",
      "startDate": "2025-04-24",
      "endDate": "2025-04-25",
      "questions": [
        {
          "question": "what is js",
          "options": [
            "java",
            "javascript",
            "ruby",
            "ang"
          ],
          "correctAnswer": "javascript"
        }
      ],
      "submitted": false
    }
  ],
  "userQuizStatus": [
    {
      "id": "0e20",
      "userId": "4ee8",
      "quizId": "c749",
      "submitted": true,
      "selectedAnswers": {
        "0": "2"
      },
      "attendedTime": "25/4/2025, 2:04:36 pm"
    },
    {
      "id": "6836",
      "userId": "189a",
      "quizId": "c749",
      "submitted": true,
      "selectedAnswers": {
        "0": "2"
      },
      "attendedTime": "25/4/2025, 2:05:02 pm"
    },
    {
      "id": "ec2b",
      "userId": "189a",
      "quizId": "52fd",
      "submitted": true,
      "selectedAnswers": {
        "0": "v2",
        "1": "Google"
      },
      "attendedTime": "25/4/2025, 2:14:18 pm"
    },
    {
      "id": "8e4a",
      "userId": "4ee8",
      "quizId": "38ed",
      "submitted": true,
      "selectedAnswers": {
        "0": "java"
      },
      "attendedTime": "25/4/2025, 3:09:03 pm"
    },
    {
      "id": "3deb",
      "userId": "4ee8",
      "quizId": "4a8b",
      "submitted": true,
      "selectedAnswers": {
        "0": "directive"
      },
      "attendedTime": "25/4/2025, 3:11:47 pm"
    },
    {
      "id": "391f",
      "userId": "4ee8",
      "quizId": "3591",
      "submitted": true,
      "selectedAnswers": {
        "0": "2"
      },
      "attendedTime": "25/4/2025, 3:18:11 pm"
    },
    {
      "id": "068d",
      "userId": "4ee8",
      "quizId": "2740",
      "submitted": true,
      "selectedAnswers": {
        "0": "2"
      },
      "attendedTime": "25/4/2025, 3:18:31 pm"
    },
    {
      "id": "ee0c",
      "userId": "189a",
      "quizId": "ba75",
      "submitted": true,
      "selectedAnswers": {
        "0": "javascript"
      },
      "attendedTime": "25/4/2025, 3:26:06 pm"
    }
  ],
  "userQuizResults": []
}